syvum.com 2006-06-15

# Syvum Privacy Policy

We at Syvum are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why Syvum has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. 

In general, you can visit syvum.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. 

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

### INFORMATION 

We want to give you information about our privacy policy and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed within our company. 

### CHILDREN UNDER 13

Syvum does not collect any information from children under 13 that could identify them. Although guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests and promotions, if such a guest wins, notification and prizes will be sent only to the parents or guardians. Publication of contest winners names for individuals under 13 require parental or guardian consent. 

### CHOICE 

There are times when we may collect personal information from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. You will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the syvum.com Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services. 

### EMAIL

_**Syvum does not engage in or support spamming or misuse of email addresses.**_

We require your email address when you register as a member to our Teens or Individual Clubs (for ages > 13). Your email address is used once to send you a welcome notice, and may be used to send emergency emails (such as a major change to our service, or to send your password if you lose/forget it). If you take part in our contests, and are a winner, your prize notification will also be sent at that address. Any other emails from Syvum will only be sent to you if you explicitly ask us to send them by subscribing to any of our optional services. 

When you use the "Send this page to a friend" feature on the Syvum web site, the email address of your friend is used only to send the requested page to them. No further emails are sent to that address, nor is that address revealed to any third party. 

_**Your email address is held in strict confidence, and only used as stated here.**_

### ACCURACY 

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future. 

### SECURITY 

We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

### COOKIES

Some parts of our site use cookies in order to provide you a better experience of the site. For example, your scores in the online activities in any given session are stored in a cookie. For registered members, cookies allow us to provide you a customized experience. Our shopping cart also uses "cookies" to make your shopping experience enjoyable. The product codes in your cart are stored in the text in the cookies. If you do not wish to use cookies, you may still shop directly from our online shop. See also: Advertisements. 

### SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Syvum may share aggregate information about its users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we may say Syvum's audience is x percent females and y percent males. This data is used to customize the content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users. 

### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We use Maxworldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here [ http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php)

In addition to MaxOnline, we also utilize the services of Adtegrity.com to serve ads on our site. To view their privacy policy, [click here](http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp). 

### THIRD PARTY COOKIES

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

### COMMITMENT 

We are committed to privacy. Personal data privacy is a new and evolving area, and Syvum is evolving to meet these demands. Mistakes are possible; miscommunication is possible. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Syvum Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the Syvum Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

Thank you for your support of these policies and of Syvum Technologies.
